us-lotteries.com 2010-06-14

# US Lotteries - Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement

##### General

This privacy Statement details our commitment to safeguard your information, and the limited manner in which we will use and disclose the information you provide to us. By using our web site, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information by us as set forth in this policy. We may from time to time change this privacy policy so please check this privacy policy regularly for any changes or updates. If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, then you may contact us. For additional information about the use of our web site, please review our Terms and Conditions of Use. 

##### Personal Information

We do not collect “Personally Identifiable Information”. By this we mean information that is specific to you as an individual, like your name, age, email address, telephone number and facsimile number. The only time we ask for your name and email address is when you contact us. And we keep that information only for our records. 

We may display or link to forms that collect personal information for companies that we are affiliates for, but the information you supply in those forms are sent directly to the merchant's web sites. We do not have control over, nor do we have access to these information. 

##### Cookies

When you visit our web site to browse, we may use cookies to collect, use and store information such as the type of computer modem and Internet browser you are using, the number of times you visit our web site and the particular pages you view, the date and time you access our site, linking to and from our site, and the length of your visits to our site. We may share this information with third parties if we choose to aggregate and disclose site traffic information to improve the use of our site for our visitors. 

Note that most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you may be able to change the settings to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you choose to modify your settings to reject cookies, it may affect your use of our web site. 

Also, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

© 2009 US-LOTTERIES.COM. All Rights Reserved.  

* * *

* * *

**• WE DO NOT SELL ANY LOTTERY, WE DO NOT BUY LOTTERY NUMBERS ON BEHALF OF ANYONE; this is only an information and guide web site.**  
• Winning numbers are obtained from official state websites and media announcements. • We are dedicated to present accurate data and calculated results, however, errors are frequently inevitable. We therefore kindly request our esteemed visitors to notify us any errors that they may come accross. • This web site makes an extensive use of JavaScript; if you have set up your computer not to run scripts, or if you are using a browser that cannot run scripts, then you will miss a large part of the fun unless you make the necessary adjustments. Our scripts do nothing else but crunch lottery numbers and deliver a well-formatted data presentation.  
• For more information read our Terms Of Use and Privacy Statements by clicking on the links below. 

* * *

* * *

Copyright © 2006-2010 US-LOTTERIES.COM
